* [Download](javascript:void();)

[English](javascript:void();)

No storage of data.  
Highly encrypted.  
Swiss made.

Data protection
===============

Last update: 20.11.2020
-----------------------

TeleGuard has an unambiguous company policy: strict observance of data protection and uncompromising protection of user privacy.

**Our services and products protect privacy.** We are aware that your privacy is of the utmost importance and take it seriously. Our TeleGuard guidelines for data protection ("Privacy policy") describe our guidelines and measures for the collection, use, publication and disclosure of your information, if you use TeleGuard. Swisscows AG is the data controller for your personal data, which is collected through the TeleGuard platform. This data protection policy applies to all activities and products of Swisscows AG and its partners and subsidiaries (combined to "TeleGuard", "we" or "us"). For clarification, personal data / information in this text refers to information that relates to an identified or identifiable person.

**What do these guidelines cover?**  
This data protection declaration (**"data protection"**) sets out the data protection declaration of Swisscows AG (hereinafter referred to as **"Swisscows"**) and applies to users (**"user"** or **"you"**) of Swisscows products, currently known as **"TeleGuard"** (**"TeleGuard"**).

This declaration applies to all products and services that we offer across our entire website, and also applies to the website and your use of TeleGuard (**"services"**). This policy does not apply to third party websites, products or services, even if their website is linked to our website. Please always check a third party's privacy practices before deciding whether to submit information. By using our website or services, you accept the practices described in this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not visit or use our website or our services. Your continued use of our website or services means that you accept this policy.

### What data do we collect?

**IP addresses**  
IP address is **NOT** saved.

**Data acquisition**  
We **do not** collect personal information from our visitors.

When using TeleGuard, your IP address is not recorded, nor do we record which browser you are using (Internet Explorer, Safari, Firefox, Chrome, etc.). It is not recorded which operating system you are using (Windows, Mac, Linux etc.), and your search queries are not recorded. The only information we store is the sum of the search queries entered daily on our website (a measure of the total traffic on our site), a breakdown of this traffic by language and pure overall statistics.

Our strict policy of not collecting any data protects your privacy. Your IP address and information about the browser and operating system could be used together with other data to clearly identify your computer, your place of residence and you. It is also important not to save any search terms, as these can also contain personal data. (Just think of someone who enters their own name and / or insurance number in the search box.)

**Geo targeting**  
In order to protect your privacy, TeleGuard completely does without statistics and analyzes of our visitors. Since we do not collect any data from our visitors, we cannot determine your place of residence either. TeleGuard does not use geo targeting.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small data packets that are stored on your computer's hard drive when you visit websites.

TeleGuard **does not** use **cookies** that could be used to identify the user.

**Data collection regarding your user account ("personal data")**  
When registering and / or purchasing on our website, you will be asked to provide the email address and payment information that you voluntarily provide to us when ordering or subscribing to our services, as well as by filling out any contact form on the website. This information is collected to properly manage your account and / or order to provide you with our customer service and, if you choose, to send you our newsletter and occasional promotional offers. The above personal information is never associated with any type of activity performed by the user within TeleGuard that is NOT recorded, logged or stored at all.

**How do we collect personal data?**  
Our website contains registration forms (e.g. during the payment process or during customer support and verification) that ask users to provide certain information, such as their email address, at their own discretion, as described in detail above. We use this information to create an account, provide customer support, send you news and updates, and promotional materials about our products or from our partners, if you requested. Under no circumstances will this information be passed on to third parties.

Users can unsubscribe from unwanted emails using the correspondingly marked option in the email or by contacting us directly via [support at teleguard.com](mailto:support at teleguard.com).

Furthermore, no cookies or other analysis tools are used in the service TeleGuard. You remain anonymous in all of our services.

**TeleGuard**  
If you use TeleGuard products or website, we know absolutely nothing about the transmitted data such as the browsing history, the destination of the data traffic, the content of the data or preferences when searching. **All of these things are NOT monitored, recorded, logged or stored by us.**

In addition, when using TeleGuard: **We do NOT collect** logs about the connections. That means: **We have NO** logs about your IP address, the time stamp of the connection or the duration of the session. **We do NOT have** access to the payment information you have provided to us and **we do NOT link** your payment or other information to any online activity within TeleGuard.

**Your rights and control:**  
Your main data protection rights in relation to your personal data that you leave or send to us are:

* (a) the right of access and information provided to you through your account;
* (b) the right to repair;
* (c) the right to delete your account;
* (d) the right to restrict processing;
* (e) the right to object to processing;
* (f) the right to data portability and
* (g) the right to withdraw consent.

We offer you the opportunity to make certain decisions and controls in connection with our treatment of your personal data that you transfer to us. Depending on your relationship with us, these choices and controls may include access to the personal information we collect about you; correction, update or deletion of any information we have associated with you. If you would like to exclude yourself from the data collection or cannot exercise your rights via your account, please contact us at: [support at teleguard.com](mailto:support at teleguard.com). If you make such a request, please note that we may need certain information from you to verify your identity and localize your data, and that the process of searching and deleting the data may take a reasonable amount of time and effort. Data protection and the associated laws in your legal system may grant you other or additional rights in connection with the data that we receive from you, which may also be applicable.

**Service performance data and summarized connection statistics from TeleGuard**  
Through our consistent **no-logs policy**, we ensure that we do **NOT** track the data traffic carried out in the TeleGuard tunnel, e.g. browsing history, traffic destination, search settings, data content, IP addresses or DNS queries. Therefore:

* We **NEVER** know which user has ever accessed a particular website or service.
* We **do NOT** know which user was connected to our TeleGuard service at a particular time or which TeleGuard server IP they were using.
* We **DO NOT know** the set of the original IP addresses of a user's computer.

**TeleGuard is 100% committed to the no-logs policy** and we do not save them. Logs can easily link actions to you, and therefore TeleGuard cannot publish such logs at any time since we **do not collect logs**.

**Children's privacy**  
You assure and guarantee that you are at least 13 years old and legally authorized to use our service. If you are under the age of 18, please read the agreement with your parents or guardians. We do not use the service to knowingly solicit or market data from children under the age of thirteen (13). We request that such persons do not provide personal data via our services. If you are aware of this or if you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has passed on information to us, please contact us at: [support at teleguard.com](mailto:support at teleguard.com).

**Update of the data protection declaration**  
If we make changes to our privacy policy at our sole discretion, those changes and updates will take effect immediately upon notification of the changed privacy policy. We therefore recommend that you regularly check this data protection declaration for updates so that you are fully informed about how your data is collected and used by the company and about your rights in this regard. The date of the last revision is shown in the heading "Last change". Your continued use of the services after notification of such changes represents your acceptance and consent to such changes to the privacy policy, and your consent to be bound by the terms of this amended statement.

If we make significant changes to this data protection declaration, we will inform you via the account or the website and will endeavor to notify you by email or by means of a notice on our website before the change takes effect.

**Our data**  
These services are owned and operated by Swisscows AG.

You can contact us:

* by post using the postal address given above,
* via our website contact form [teleguard.com/en/imprint,](https://teleguard.com/en/imprint)
* via email to [support at teleguard.com](mailto:support at teleguard.com).

**Data protection officer**  
If you have any questions about data protection, please send us an email or contact the person responsible for data protection in our organization directly:

Swisscows AG  
Bucherstrasse 2  
9322 Egnach  
Switzerland  

About TeleGuard About MyVoice TeleGuard is a messenger that does not store chats and does not share data. The chats as well as voice and video calls are end-to-end encrypted. After delivery, messages are immediately deleted from the servers. All files are automatically deleted after one month at the latest. No data remains in the system. Discover the MyVoice app as your solution for the instant transmission of spoken translation in real time. The MyVoice app is perfect for events, online meetings and other functions. Experience seamless translation transmission without time delays.

About Swisscows Our passion is to protect people from monitoring.  
As Swisscows team we have made it our mission to provide a protected space for Internet users. Our search engine Swisscows is just the beginning! We have set out to create safe alternatives in all areas!

Swisscows AG  
Bucherstrasse 2,  
9322 Egnach,  
Switzerland

©2024, [Swisscows AG](https://company.swisscows.ch/)

ATTENTION!
==========

By downloading and installing this app from the APK you accept the term that if the functionality of the app varies from the official download pages (Google Play and App Store), you waive any claims. You further accept full responsibility for checking for and installing updates.

**Please note that APK installation is not compatible with Play Store installation. This means that the app can only be updated from the same source it was installed from.**

**Also, when updating the application through the APK, we strongly recommend that you make backups. In case of any problems, you can reinstall the application and recover your data.**

[Download  
APK file](https://pub.teleguard.com/teleguard-latest.apk) [](javascript:void();)

ATTENTION!
==========

**Starting in 2024, developers will have to pay even more to bypass the Microsoft Defender warning window on Windows. If you know why you need TeleGuard, just make a few extra clicks when you first install it from the official website.**

Hardly anyone thinks about the fact that the lack of a Microsoft Defender warning window via an unknown source means the developer has to pay a tidy sum to third-party certification companies whose prices and requirements are regularly increased.

Both Linux and Apple macOS provide similar tools for free and directly.

An alternative to buying a CodeSign certificate would be to host the application on the Microsoft Store platform, which is inextricably linked to telemetry and the collection of Windows user data.

As an independent company developing software focused on privacy and online security, we consider this to be merely an artificially created system that serves the purposes of Microsoft and NOT the end user.

Based on the above, we decided to refuse to purchase “empty air” and provide TeleGuard “as is”, leaving the choice to the user.

[_MS Windows (8.0+)_](https://pub.teleguard.com/teleguard-desktop-latest.exe) [](javascript:void();)

Two options are available for installation. An installation from the Snap Store (recommended) with the benefit of an automatic update, or from a deb package with external dependencies downloaded from public locations (in this case the application can only be updated manually).

* To install the application via SNAP, run the command  
    sudo snap install teleguard-desktop  
    in the terminal, or click the button to access the web version of the Snap Store.
* To install the application from a deb package, download the file using the button below and then open it using either "Install Applications" or "Install Software" (right-click on the .deb file, select "Open with...", then "All Applications" and select "Install Applications"/"Install Software" from the list). In the window that appears, click "Install ". All necessary dependencies will be automatically downloaded from the public locations.

[DOWNLOAD  
.DEB](https://pub.teleguard.com/teleguard-desktop-latest.deb) [](https://snapcraft.io/teleguard-desktop)

[](javascript:void();)
